CARLOS MARTÍNEZ

FULL STACK JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER

CONTACT

linkedin:

https://linkedin.com/in/coxato

github:

https://github.com/coxato

upwork profile:

https://www.upwork.com/freelancers/~01eb90cff165703930

website:

https://coxato.dev

Email:

carlosmandolina18@gmail.com

SKILLS

JavaScript

React.js

React Native

Redux

Next.js

Node.js

Express.js

MongoDB

Firebase

Python MySQL

Git & github

PORTFOLIO

https://coxato.dev

ABOUT

Full stack JavaScript programmer with more than 5 years of experience building modern web applications. I work mostly with the MERN stack (MongoDB, Express, React, Node), I also have knowledge of React Native, firebase, python, git & github. I always give my best and I'm willing to learn new things.

Take a look at my work or get in touch! https://coxato.dev

EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

WEBARY Web Development | Nov 2021 - present

- Building dashboards with React.js
- Design and build backend with express.js and MongoDB.
- Optimize image and video loading.
- Work with canvas.
- UX/UI scripts for several webpages.

WEB DEVELOPER

libraryaudio.com | Apr 2021 - Jun 2021

- Building frontend for libraryaudio.com
- Scripts for WordPress plugins.
- Work with a lot of audio files and making custom players.
- Teamwork with graphic designer to implement corporate identity on websites.

WEB DEVELOPER

ASX asx.mx | Feb 2020 - Jul 2020

- Building modern web apps with React.js and Firebase.
- Making React Native apps.
- Building admin dashboards.

FREELANCER

Self Employed | Jan 2018 - present

- Building websites for freelance jobs.
- Scripts for WordPress plugins.
- React Native apps.

EDUCATION

FULL STACK JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER

Platzi | 2018 - 2020

Platzi is an online school for learn software development, graphic design and marketing, in this school I took the "JavaScript School career" where they teach the entire JavaScript ecosystem (frontend and backend)

you can see my platzi profile https://platzi.com/@cems/And of course I'm a self-taught developer.

COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Universidad Politécnica Territorial de los Llanos Juana Ramirez | 2018 - 2023